[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these was invented by William E. Spicer, a Professor of Engineering at Stanford University?", "correct_answer": "Night vision goggles", "incorrect_answers": ["Stealth technology", "CrazyGlue", "Portable dialysis machines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first movie in which Denzel Washington starred?", "correct_answer": "Carbon Copy", "incorrect_answers": ["Cry Freedom", "Glory", "Malcolm X"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main cause for most pandemics in history?", "correct_answer": "The domestication of animals", "incorrect_answers": ["Human negligence", "Genetic experiments", "The bad hygiene of the people"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2004 movie has 3 different stories from the minds of 3 different directors from 3 different Asian countries.", "correct_answer": "Three Extremes", "incorrect_answers": ["Hero", "The Grudge", "Audition"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This black comedy was loosely based on the O. Henry short story The Ransom of Red Chief.", "correct_answer": "Ruthless People", "incorrect_answers": ["The Witches of Eastwick", "Moonstruck", "The Secret of My Success"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bernie Mac has a clown at his car lot when he sells Bumblebee to Sam Witwicky in the film Transformers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Giraffes need less sleep than nearly every other animal.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many stanzas is The Philippine National Anthem composed of?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "6", "7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Up In Smoke the characters, played by Cheech and Chong compete in The Rock Fight of the Century in which L. A. bar?", "correct_answer": "The Roxy", "incorrect_answers": ["Fever", "House of Punk", "Smittys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which grapefruit variety contains the powerful antioxidant lycopene?", "correct_answer": "Red grapefruit", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "White grapefruit", "Yellow grapefruit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the award for best actor in a leading role at the 78th Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Philip Seymour Hoffman", "incorrect_answers": ["George Clooney", "Joaquin Phoenix", "Terrence Howard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote and performed the 2005 song Bad Day?", "correct_answer": "Daniel Powter", "incorrect_answers": ["Taylor Hicks", "Green Day", "Alvin"]}]